{
    "subject": "resource/Point_Arguello_Launch_Complex_B",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedRocket",
    "object": "resource/Nike-Viper",
    "human_readable": "The Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with the Nike-Viper rocket.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9619414806365967,
            "question": "Which rocket is linked to the Point Arguello Launch Complex B?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9583551287651062,
            "question": "Name the rocket used at the Point Arguello Launch Complex B."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9514483213424683,
            "question": "What is the Point Arguello Launch Complex B associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308117985725403,
            "question": "What type of launch facility is the Point Arguello Launch Complex B?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7780621647834778,
            "question": "Where is the Point Arguello Launch Complex B located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7629028558731079,
            "question": "Is there a specific rocket program associated with this launch complex?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6270512938499451,
            "question": "How has the use of the Point Arguello Launch Complex B evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6142019629478455,
            "question": "What was the purpose of using the Nike-Viper rocket?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4278382360935211,
            "question": "Were there any notable achievements or failures associated with launches from this complex?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2688637673854828,
            "question": "What other historical launches might have taken place at this complex?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with the Nike-Viper rocket.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5841_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable achievements or failures associated with launches from this complex?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5841_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the purpose of using the Nike-Viper rocket?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5841_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the use of the Point Arguello Launch Complex B evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5841_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5841_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\nThe provided document indeed mentions that the Nike-Viper was one of the rockets launched from LC-B at the Point Arguello Naval Air Station. Thus, it supports the statement that The Point Arguello Launch Complex B is associated with the Nike-Viper rocket."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}